Attack with cannon, and end turn.
Dang, Hazuki, you're good!
Okay, one more match. I'm not gonna quit until I win at least one of these.
Okay, but you realize that means you're never going home.
Wise guy, eh?
I can't believe we finally caught you without your sister.
Come on, you don't have to say it like that.
Hey, guys! Can we play too?
We've got decks and all, but I don't know. The rules are kind of hard to understand.
You're good at this, right, Kazuki?
Huh?
If you don't mind, could you teach me a few tricks?
Oh, uh, sure.
Uh…
Should I get to it?
Alright.
Oh, there we go.
A immortal mystery person
I cannot do so much
There are a story
Thank you.
Oh, and you can still sign up the day of the event, so don't be afraid to stop by and check it out.
Um, cool.
So?
I'll be done in a few minutes. Hang tight.
Cool.
Yuzuki?
Sorry. What do you think? Are we in or what?
Participating as a selector without having a wish is more than just wrong. It's blasphemy.
I'm going either way.
I might even find another selector to battle.
Yeah, but my wish already.
Right. It already came true.
Uh-huh. So if I won, it wouldn't be fair to the person I beat. There's no need to be greedy after all.
But if the other player isn't a selector, it'll be fine. Meaning we're free to fight all the dudes we want.
Good point. As long as nobody's dreams are at stake, I'm definitely up for a battle or two.
Yeah.
Sure. That sounds okay. I suppose I'm on board.
If nothing else, it's a chance to try out my new deck.
Right, Midoriko?
Midoriko?
Oh.
Okay, sweet!
So ladies, I was thinking about Momoka's idea for us to match our outfits. We could be like a pop-through. Huh?
That's cute, but kind of pricey.
Yeah, we spend too much on cards. Oh well.
Oh, hey, look!
Now that's more in our price range.
It's not quite as fancy, but we can still match with these.
Scrunchies, huh?
Mm-hmm.
We might not look much like a pop-through, but try it.
Well, you gotta go with green to match your deck.
Oh, cool. I found a red one.
Ruko's deck is white.
Oh, no luck.
You can take this weird-looking one instead.
Don't give me the icky one!
How's this?
You're picking ugly ones up perfect!
Stop it!
Okay, sorry.
And then we all brought these matching scrunchies.
That's lovely, and I'm thrilled that you're making new friends. But your hair is still wet from your shower. Your scrunchie is going to mess it up.
It's fine. So anyway, Ruko almost got this weird-looking one, but she ended up with Aqua instead, even though her deck is white.
All right, you can tell me all about it later.
But first, go dry your hair and put something warmer on. You're going to catch your death.
Yes, ma'am.
Aw, it did get all messed up.
Yeah, and the scrunchie's all damp, too!
Of course it is.
Aw, I'm so stupid.
Hitae?
Yeah, what is it?
I think it's best if you get rid of me.
Get rid of you? Why?
Your wish already came true. There's no need for you to battle anymore.
Sure, but who cares about that? I like you a whole bunch, Midoriko. I would never want to get rid of you.
I'm afraid that if you keep me, something might happen. Something terrible.
So what?
Before I even met Ruko and Yuzuki, you were my friend, Midoriko, and nothing will change that.
Oh, Hitoi.
I don't want to hear you talk like that ever again.
Oh, yeah! Still need to dry my hair.
Aw, I suck.
Something wrong?
Not really. I just can't get my hair tied up right, that's all.
You are kind of clumsy with that stuff. Here, let me get it for you.
Huh? No, it's fine! Really!
Don't freak out.
I'm not freaking out. I just need to learn.
It's cold.
Oh, here, look. There's a big giraffe on the building.
Cool!
Is it gonna battle the other giraffe?
Tama, not everything is about battles, you know.
I am right.
So battle me.
Iona was really pretty, but, uh, she was also kind of scary. Don't you think?
Tama can beat all the scaries!
Looks like I'm here a bit early.
I made it to the meeting spot.
I'll be waiting.
And sit.
It's funny, but when I'm standing in a big crowd like this, I almost feel like a normal girl.
Come on, Hitaway. You are a normal girl.
I'll take your word for it.
It's nice out.
When I first moved to Tokyo, somehow I felt like there wasn't a sky here, thanks to all the skyscrapers and stuff.
But there it is. As bright and blue as it's ever been.
All this time I never noticed.
How sad.
I just needed to look up.
Hitaway.
Drop me!
Throw me away now!
Please!
Hurry!
Rugo, let's go!
I'm sorry!
There were a whole bunch of people in the bathroom and the kid behind me was about to go in her pants, so I let her cut in line!
Hmm, we're making Hitaway wait!
Okay, okay!
Huh.
She said she'd be here.
Too short, I can't see!
Guessing you came up empty too?
Uh-huh.
She isn't answering my texts either.
Maybe she got mad at us because we were late.
She wouldn't lose her temper over something like that.
Right? Back me up on this, Hanayou.
Hanayou?
Oh, yeah, of course.
Field!
Something going on, Tama?
There's a battlefield somewhere!
Close!
What? Around here?
Hitaway!
What?
They're strong.
Really strong!
Adyoyako!
I'm sorry!
No!
Don't worry about me!
But it's my fault!
You're suffering!
I'll try to end this quickly, okay?
I don't need to win!
I'll lose on purpose!
Please, you have to keep fighting!
You can't give up!
It's fine!
Really!
The only wish I wanted already came true!
And now neither one of us have to go through these painful battles anymore!
Ito-
Ito-e!
Listen!
Huh?!
There's something important I haven't told you!
What do you mean?
You know all about winning, and becoming an eternal girl!
Your wish!
Ito-e!
Hito-e! Where did you go? Sorry, mister!
Hito-e!
However, you don't know what it means to lose.
Tama, we close?
The battlefield... wait, bye-bye.
Hey, Hanayo, do you know anything about this?
Hey, look!
Hito-e!
There you are! You had us all worried!
Hito-e, what's wrong?
Wh-what do you want?
How do you know my name?
If this is a joke, I don't get it.
Hey, wait!
What the? Are you okay?
Hito-e! Tell us what's wrong!
Stand back! Don't touch her!
Whoever you are, leave me alone!
I don't-
Hito-e! Lost!
What?
Tama is not sensing her selector power!
She had a battle and lost!
No!
Are you saying she's not a selector anymore?
Did something messed up happen to her because she lost her third battle?
What is this?
Hanayo!
What?
After three losses, your status as a selector is revoked.
As for your wish, it becomes corrupted.
Ugh! You mean like you get a curse?
Yes.
For example, let's say your wish was to become wealthy.
After losing three battles, not only would that wish fail to come true, you would plummet into poverty.
If your wish was to be an expert pianist, you wouldn't just lose your piano.
Something would happen that would prevent you from playing ever again.
Something to ensure your wish could never come true.
That's awful!
I'm not really getting this.
So what happened to Hito-e?
All I can tell you is her wish was to make friends.
You can imagine what a corruption of that would be.
So you're saying she lost her friends?
Far worse than that.
She can never make friends again.
You saw what state she was in.
Seems if anyone has even the potential to be her friend.
Her body goes through some sort of violent shock when they try to approach her.
No way!
Horrible.
But unfortunately, there's more.
With her third loss, not only is her selector status gone,
so are all her memories related to those battles.
As if they never even took place.
What is this?
What's happening?
I'm scared.
Hito-e, what's wrong?
How do they know me?
Who were they?
That didn't hurt me.
Why?
Oh God!
Why does this hurt?
I can't know!
It hurts just thinking about them.
They can stop!
That's it!
I'll win and wish for Hito-e to go back to normal!
I finally have a dream worth fighting for!
I didn't think of that.
Right!
It won't work.
What?
Even though it didn't happen as a result of winning battles,
her wish did come true.
The corruption cannot be undone by another selector's wish.
What the hell?!
That's kind of an important detail you decided to keep secret from me!
Damn it! Why won't you say something?!
How do you?!
Ah!
Yeah, the sky would get cloudy, wouldn't it?
Looks like rain soon, too.
I know I don't have any right to cry.
You don't have any right to cry. After ruining such an innocent wish, any fate I face will be too kind.
I really did care for you, Heetui. And yet, after this, I wish that we had never even met each other.
Goodbye.
I trusted you all this time, Hanio.
I trusted you all this time, Hanio. I don't know what to do. I'm afraid of you.
You can get rid of me. It'll be easy. Just throw me away.
That's not funny!
Yuzuki, something wrong?
It's nothing. I'm okay.
Were you fighting with Hanio?
No.
Tell me. I'm here for you.
You wouldn't say that if you knew the truth.
I mean, we've been together our whole lives.
What if I just told him?
Yuzuki?
Really, I'm fine.
Don't worry about me!
I see.
You don't want to tell me.
Okay.
If you don't need me, it's fine.
Oh, Kazuki, I...
Hello?
Oh, hey.
Real good, thanks.
Tomorrow, huh?
And everyone is coming?
No, that should be okay, but...
No, I'll be there.
Sounds good.
Yeah, see ya.
I hate this.
I hate this so much.
This is really neat!
We've never been here before!
I guess not.
I usually only come to sit down restaurants like this with Grandma.
You're not going home?
No, I can't.
Not yet.
Whenever I fail a test or hide something from Grandma,
she knows right away.
Woo!
Tama, did you know?
Nuh-uh.
I don't know anything.
Everything's all fuzzy and white in Tama's head,
so I can't think at all.
But I...
I love battles!
I know that much!
And I want more!
And I don't like Bruce sad.
I don't want that.
Tama.
I found you!
Paralux said a battle happened around here,
so I came to check it out.
I figured it might be Yuzupu and the gals,
so I sent a text to her and Hitoi to see what was up, you know?
Yuzupu was too mean to reply, but Hitoi...
Well, look, it's like she didn't even know who I was anymore.
Guess she lost her third match and got kicked to the curve, huh?
You've known all along what happens to selectors
and you never told anyone?
What the heck is this today?
Come here.
Let's have a potty party!
Um, what are you...
So, funny story, the first time I saw a selector battle,
it wasn't even mine, it was Yona's.
Huh?
On my way out from a photo shoot,
I guess she was picking a fight with some other selector
because I got pulled into their field out of the blue.
She could have warned me, right?
Anywho, her opponent had already lost two battles
and was at the end of her rope.
She was all, like, huffing and puffing
and just super sick looking.
I could tell she wanted to win real bad, though.
Well, Yona didn't give a crap.
Long story short, there was a lot of thrashing
and not much in the way of happy endings.
When it was over, she must have had a stroke or something.
It was bad, like ambulance and everything.
I don't know if you heard,
but Yona's L-rig is super sadistic.
That poor girl didn't stand a chance.
Do you know what happened to her?
None of my business, really.
I mean, I saw that she got taken to the hospital,
but she was looking pretty bad,
so it's tough to say.
No, that's terrible.
I know, like, for serious.
Compared to something like that.
Not being able to make friends isn't so bad, right?
How did you know?
You forgot already?
When we fought, I did that awesome thing
where I could see her wish?
Well, she wasn't exactly Miss Popularity to begin with.
So who cares?
This is kind of a plus for you, really.
Now you don't have to humor the poor disaster anymore.
Banging around her wasn't doing you any favors.
I mean, seriously, she was super frumpy.
At least now she knows nobody will be her friend,
so she doesn't have to latch on to people like a parasite.
So yeah, even if she doesn't make friends,
it's pretty much better for everyone that way.
That's really what you think, huh?
Huh?
Yeah, of course.
So anyway, I...
You take that back!
Not gonna do it!
Listen up!
You take it back,
or I will never forgive you!
Wow!
I am, like, really scared!
You must think super highly of yourself, huh?
I can't live if Ruu won't forgive me!
You know,
if you truly can't forgive me,
why don't we have a battle?
I mean,
if you beat me bad enough,
maybe I'll cry
and see the error of my wicked old ways!
Yeah, fine.
No!
We can battle.
And after I beat you,
we're going to visit Hitome.
See, you can tell my friend that you're sorry!
I'll see you next time.